<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Maleko &#8211; Maleko</title>
	<atom:link href="/category/maleko/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Best in Class Fragnance</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 09:04:05 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.3.1</generator>
	<item>
		<title>How To Make A Deodorant Bottle Last Longer?</title>
		<link>/how-to-make-a-deodorant-bottle-last-longer/</link>
					<comments>/how-to-make-a-deodorant-bottle-last-longer/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Abhi6722]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 21 May 2022 08:10:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Maleko]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://maleko.abhi6722.in/?p=127</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bodysprays and deodorants are common perfume products that are used on regular basis by the Indian masses. They are affordable, easy to use, and are widely available everywhere from drugstores to online perfume stores. With so many benefits, there is one con that makes deodorants less desirable to many of the fragrance users and it [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Bodysprays and deodorants are common perfume products that are used on regular basis by the Indian masses. They are affordable, easy to use, and are widely available everywhere from drugstores to online perfume stores. With so many benefits, there is one con that makes deodorants less desirable to many of the fragrance users and it is the longevity. The deodorant bottle can last only about 20 days maximum if you are using them twice daily. if you are also facing this issue and want your deodorant to last longer for at least a month, these simple tips will come in handy,</p>



<p><strong>Use it sparingly:</strong></p>



<p>Are you habitual of spraying on the perfumed body spray all over your body and clothes? Are you spraying more than three times all over with long spray? Well, this is the biggest reason to make the perfume body spray finish sooner than you expected. Try to avoid doing it if you wish to make your perfumed body spray last longer. Spray the&nbsp;<strong>deodorant for men</strong>&nbsp;or women in small spritzes thrice or four times on pulse points of your body. You can refresh the aroma by spraying on your clothes as well as keeping the sprays small.</p>



<p><strong>Spray from a distance:</strong></p>



<p>Never spray by keeping the deodorant can close to your body. Keep the spray nozzle at least 10 centimeters as it will help in spreading the spray to a large space, covering more area on your skin. With 3 or 4 short sprays you can cover the almost entire area on your upper body. Keeping the nozzle closer to the skin wastes too much product while making the skin prone to getting rashes and damage.</p>



<p><strong>Invest in good brands:</strong></p>



<p>This is one thing that can impact your usage of body sprays a lot. If you are buying poor quality deodorants available at a cheap price, these tend to evaporate faster due to low perfume essence. Get a lasting fragrance with body sprays from top international brands. These&nbsp;<a href="https://www.perfumebooth.com/deodorant"><strong>deodorant</strong></a>&nbsp;sprays contain a high perfume essence concentration which eventually enhances longevity. To get better results, try to get deodorant from brands like Lomani, Louis Cardin, R&amp;R, New NB, Colour Me, and such other popular perfume brands that created deodorants for their perfume counterparts. With this, you can enjoy a lasting fragrance for up to 6 hours.</p>



<p><strong>Follow the basic perfume rules:</strong></p>



<p>If you are a regular perfume user, you must be aware of all the basic perfume etiquettes that help in enjoying the fragrance for longer making the bottle last more than ever. Spray the perfumed deodorant for women or men on your skin after cleansing the skin well. Take bath or clean the skin using wet tissue paper. Moisturize your skin properly using unscented moisturizer and then spray the body spray on your skin keeping it at a distance.</p>



<p>These tips are easy to follow and perfect for making your body spray last longer. Follow them, use good quality deodorants and you can save on your monthly perfume budget as well.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/how-to-make-a-deodorant-bottle-last-longer/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>5 Deodorant Mistakes That You Need To Avoid Making</title>
		<link>/5-deodorant-mistakes-that-you-need-to-avoid-making/</link>
					<comments>/5-deodorant-mistakes-that-you-need-to-avoid-making/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Abhi6722]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 21 May 2022 08:09:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Maleko]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://maleko.abhi6722.in/?p=124</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Using a deodorant after a bath or during the day is a common routine for everyone. some may even carry it with them to freshen up after sports or gym or a run. Yet, there are several mistakes that we make while using deodorants. These can reduce the ability of your deodorants to work affecting [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Using a deodorant after a bath or during the day is a common routine for everyone. some may even carry it with them to freshen up after sports or gym or a run. Yet, there are several mistakes that we make while using deodorants. These can reduce the ability of your deodorants to work affecting their fragrance. If you think that your deodorant is not working, these might help,</p>



<p><strong>Understanding The Difference Between Deodorant And Antiperspirant:</strong></p>



<p>Deodorants&nbsp;help in eradicating the body stink and have fragrance in them. These help in killing the odour-causing bacteria or cover it with an aromatic scent. Contrary to it, antiperspirants are for reducing your sweat and may or may not have a scent in them. Before choosing the right body spray, you will have to understand your need.</p>



<p>If you sweat too much, go for the body spray with antiperspirant properties. If you smell bad, deodorants are for you. There are&nbsp;<strong>deo for girls</strong>&nbsp;and boys that come only with scent as well having neither properties.</p>



<p><strong>Reapplying Deodorant On Dirty Skin:</strong></p>



<p>It is a common habit to apply deodorant whenever you feel the need throughout the day. This can make your deodorant spray smell weird and stinky. Another mistake is to spray on dirty sweaty clothes. It will only mask the smell by adding a strong odour to it. After an hour or so, you will again smell bad. Instead, try to wear clean and fresh clothes every day.</p>



<p><strong>Avoid Spraying Immediately After Shaving:</strong></p>



<p><strong>Body sprays for men</strong>&nbsp;and women have chemicals and alcohol. When you spray it on freshly shaved skin, it will make it sting bad. you can also experience irritation, burning, and redness on your skin. If you have sensitive skin and wish to avoid this, take some time before spraying. You can also apply some talc before deo to reduce burning.</p>



<p><strong>Discolouring Clothes:</strong></p>



<p>If your clothes have started to discolor because of body spray, this will help you. Body sprays have talc and certain other chemicals which can discolor your clothes. Next time allows your body spray to dry before wearing clothes. You must also avoid spraying these on your apparel as well.</p>



<p><strong>Avoiding Moisturisation:</strong></p>



<p>Like perfumes, deodorants work better if you apply moisturiser prior to the application. Take an unscented body lotion, apply it to your skin and top it with deodorant. This will protect your skin from irritation and make the scent last for long. You can use any lotion, body oil or moisturising cream for this.</p>



<p>For smelling great with&nbsp;<strong>deodorants</strong>, you should try international brands. Body Sprays from Lomani, Baug Sons, Louis Cardin, Colour Me, and Chris Adams are very aromatic. These perfumed body sprays have fragrances lasting up to 6 hours. You can smell fresh for hours with ease using them. If you spend more time outside and need to smell good, trying these is worth it. Explore a wide range of international deodorants online on Perfume Booth. You can get the best deals on international body sprays for men and women here.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/5-deodorant-mistakes-that-you-need-to-avoid-making/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How Should I Apply Deodorant For Lasting Freshness?</title>
		<link>/how-should-i-apply-deodorant-for-lasting-freshness/</link>
					<comments>/how-should-i-apply-deodorant-for-lasting-freshness/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Abhi6722]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 21 May 2022 08:01:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Maleko]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://maleko.abhi6722.in/?p=122</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Deodorants are one of the most affordable ways to smell good. Available in a can, these are easy to carry around anywhere you like. You can keep them in your car or gym bag, stock one in office drawer or bathroom. But often these perfumed body sprays are not able to give you lasting aroma. [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Deodorants are one of the most affordable ways to smell good. Available in a can, these are easy to carry around anywhere you like. You can keep them in your car or gym bag, stock one in office drawer or bathroom. But often these perfumed body sprays are not able to give you lasting aroma. there are several reasons behind this. You might have been using it in a wrong way. Or bought a body spray not meant for your needs. Quite like perfumes, deodorants are also tricky to use. Understanding the type, you need, fragrance it has and even how much you sprayed on will help a lot.</p>



<p><strong>What Are The Several Types Of Body Sprays Available?</strong></p>



<p>There are several types of body sprays available in India. Deodorants are the ones with antibacterial properties. They help in eradicating smell-causing bacteria and staying fresh for hours. Anyone with smelly sweat can try these. Another one is the antiperspirants variant which helps in reducing your sweating. If you sweat too much and worry about sweat patches on your clothes, this is for you.</p>



<p>Apart from these two body spray variants, there is one more, perfumed sprays. These types of body sprays will only give you a good smell. It does not have any effect on sweat or eradicate body odor. For having the best results from your body spray, make sure to get the one you need.</p>



<p><strong>Best Way To Apply Deodorant For A Lasting Scent:</strong></p>



<p>Deodorants or perfumed body sprays will not work as they should without proper use. If you will spray them on dirty skin or your clothes, these will evaporate in no time. Even the&nbsp;<a href="https://www.perfumebooth.com/best-body-spray-for-men"><strong>best body spray for men</strong></a>&nbsp;will not work in this situation. For making it last longer, you should spray the deodorant sprays only on clean and fresh skin. Take a bath and towel dry your skin to remove any unnecessary moisture. Now apply some body lotion or cream to hydrate your skin and prep it for deo. Applying body spray on prepped skin helps it to absorb the molecules.</p>



<p>Never spray the deodorant on your clothes. They will only work in a proper way if you apply deodorant to your skin. Moreover, your skin is able to hold on to perfume molecules, making it last longer. Otherwise, it will evaporate in no time. Another helpful way to make your deo last long is to freshen up every 3-4 hours. Spray your deo again on the same spot. This will help in preventing the aroma from evaporating completely. Last but not the least, the distance between the spray and your body. Keep the nozzle a few inches away while spraying. This will help in covering larger space.</p>



<p>Enjoy a lasting freshness with branded international deodorants. Buy trending&nbsp;<strong>best Deo for men in 2022&nbsp;</strong>from top brands like Baug Sons, Lomani, Chris Adams, Otoori and, Rich and Ruitz. If you need relief from sweaty odor, try sports deo from Hot Ice. All these brands are known for highly aromatic body sprays. For a perfume like an experience, try Colour Me body sprays for men and women. All these international brands are now available on Perfume Booth at an affordable price.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/how-should-i-apply-deodorant-for-lasting-freshness/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
